This time, I'll be the dealer.
（静火(しずか)）今回は私が親です
Best regards.
（裁園寺(さいおんじ)）よろしく
By the way,
what cards are you living on now?
（代銀(しろがね)）ところで君は
今は どのカードで生活している？
You must have a good hand.
いい手札がそろったはずだ
I leave that to your imagination.
（静火）ご想像にお任せします
Case No. 10785, Inspect Relation start.
（ラウンドロビン）
第一〇七八五号事案
インスペクト･リレーションを
スタート
Debate: leading candidate, Karina Komiya.
審議 優先候補 小宮(こみや)カリナ
Security item:
Tokyo gubernatorial election.
セキュリティー項目
東京都知事選挙
Relation Block: Criminal Investigation
Department Unit One.
リレーションブロック
公安局刑事課一係
Now, it's finally time.
（代銀）さあ いよいよだ
This will be a major turning point
for us here at Bifrost.
我々ビフロストにとって
ここは大きな分かれ目となる
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
♪～
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the lost memories that flee
once they're liberated and banished
Are an everlasting cubism.
Cause I know that in a future gone mad,
Even nightmares are peaceful.
RESET, RESET, yeah.
The midnight sun
awakens and turns to a riot.
A gun for a faux-friendly kiss.
A knife for a faux-revolutionary hug.
Get rid of it all, even the frozen chains.
Reality is always outside your head.
In a world seen through bestial eyes,
There is neither darkness nor light.
Draw the knives
locked behind your eyelids.
Reap the lives that grow into shackles.
Even the false memories that flash before
your eyes impatiently and impulsively
Are an everlasting cubism.
～♪
#03
Herakles and the Sirens
Thank you for your cooperation.
（炯(けい)）ご協力
ありがとうございます
You have two minutes.
We can't spare any more.
（リー）２分だ
それ以上の時間はない
Do you know a man named Kojo Tsuchiya?
（炯）土谷荒城(つちやこうじょう)という人物を
ご存じですか？
I don't. Will that be all?
（薬師寺(やくしじ)）知らない
これで終わりでいいかね？
Candidate Komiya is currently in the lead.
Do you have a plan to turn that around?
（炯）現在 小宮候補に
リードされていますが―
何か打開策が？
Ask my first secretary, Lee, about that.
（薬師寺）それは
第一秘書のリーに聞いてくれ
A slight disadvantage was anticipated.
多少の不利は想定内です
She seems to be ahead in Sibyl System's
politician suitability as well.
（炯）シビュラシステムの
政治家適正でも不利なようですが
A negligible difference.
（リー）僅かな差だ
I won't deny that I'm losing.
負けていることは否定しない
But I have overcome strict
daily training and many deadly struggles.
しかし日々の厳しい鍛錬と―
多くの死闘を乗り越えた
私の色相が―
My Hue will triumph in the end.
最後に必ず勝つ
Can martial arts really clear your Hue?
（天馬(てんま)）格闘技で
色相はクリアになりますかね？
Of course.
A healthy mind dwells in a healthy body.
もちろんだ
健全な精神は健全な肉体に宿る
I don't get it. It's just a way to beat up
people who piss you off, right?
分かんねえなあ
所詮 むかつく相手を
ぶちのめす手段でしょうが
You're an enforcer, aren't you?
（薬師寺）君は執行官だね？
What about it?
（天馬）それが何か？
（薬師寺）だい！
（天馬）うう…
What a pitiful man you are!
（天馬）え…
（薬師寺）君は実に悲しい男だ！
Don't give up just because
you're a latent criminal!
潜在犯だからって諦めるな！
Love yourself! Fight for it!
自分を愛せ！
そのために闘うんだよ！
It's not too late for you! Live strong!
君は まだ間に合う
強く生きろ！
Mr. Yakushiji.
（リー）薬師寺先生
What?
（薬師寺）何だ？
The two minutes we gave them are up.
（リー）約束の２分が過ぎています
Oh, right!
（薬師寺）そうか
Your car has arrived, sir.
（一童）先生 お車が到着しました
（一童･春馬）ん…
Do your best. Keep at it.
（薬師寺）頑張れよ 頑張れ！
What is it? You know him?
どうした？　知り合いか？
No.
いえ
He is the shame of the Todoroki family.
我が廿六木(とどろき)一族の恥さらしです
Please forget him.
お忘れください
It sounds like there's a story there...
（薬師寺）
何やら事情がありそうだが…
Well, I look forward to your support!
それじゃ 応援よろしく！
（ドアの閉まる音）
So, an enforcer has relatives
working on the Yakushiji campaign?
薬師寺陣営に執行官の家族… か
（舌打ち）
Dr. Tsuchiya specialized in neuroscience.
（灼(あらた)）土谷博士の専門は脳科学
Particularly, self-control via stereotypes
in the decision-making process.
（灼）特に 意思決定過程での―
固定観念による
セルフコントロールを―
テーマにしてたみたいです
What does that mean?
（入江(いりえ)）そりゃ何ですか？
One experiment with negative
and positive stereotypes
（灼）否定的固定観念と
肯定的固定観念の実験に―
goes like this:
こういうのがあります
First, you take students of equal academic
ability and split them into two groups.
まず学力が同レベルの学生を集めて
２つのグループに分ける
You tell group A they're poor students
グループＡには
“君たちは劣等生組だ”と告げ―
and tell group B they're
the advanced class.
グループＢには
“優等生組だ”と告げる
Then, you have them take a test.
そして テストを受けさせる
Even though they're intellectually equal,
there's a gap in their scores,
すると 本当は
学力に差がないのに―
なぜか点差が出るってわけか
right?
Acting strong is all it takes
to make the human brain
人間の脳は
強いふりをするだけで―
secrete testosterone,
a hormone that encourages risk-taking.
リスクを取る行動を促すホルモン
テストステロンを分泌するんです
In contrast, acting weak
逆に 弱いふりをすると―
causes it to secrete
the stress-relief hormone cortisol.
ストレス発散ホルモンである
コルチゾールが分泌されます
Huh. So, what's that got to do
with the accident?
（入江）へえ
で 事故に関係あります？
Something, I hope.
（灼）うーん あるといいな～
You seem pretty fixated
on this accident, Inspector.
（入江）監視官が
こういう事故に こだわる理由
Are you following orders
from Chief Shimotsuki?
もしかして
霜月(しもつき)課長の命令ですか？
No, just my intuition.
いえ 単に俺の勘ですよ
Intuition, huh?
勘… ね
Karina will be the next governor for sure.
（女性）やっぱカリナだよね
次の都知事は
Yeah.
I definitely hope she is.
（女性）うん 絶対なってほしい
We need to Karina to keep
those people under control.
早くカリナに あの人たちを
しっかり管理してもらわないと
I know.
Just looking at them clouds my Hue.
（女性）ホント 見かけるだけで
色相 曇っちゃう
（女性たち）ん？
Good afternoon, young ladies.
（梓澤(あずさわ)）ごきげんよう お嬢様方
Having English-style afternoon tea?
英国式のアフタヌーンティーですか
うーん
Might I suggest coffee?
コーヒーにしましょう
After all, English tea culture
イギリスの
紅茶文化なんてものは―
only began because they lost a trade war.
貿易戦争に負けて
しかたなく始まったもんですから
（女性たち）あ…
By the way, I'm the owner of this café.
（梓澤）ああ わたくし
このカフェのオーナーです
（メールの受信音）
Case No. 10785, is it?
（梓澤）
“第一〇七八五号事案”ね…
OK.
オッケー
First Inspector.
I will resume my duties as floorman.
ファースト･インスペクター
フロアマンとして
活動を続行します
I know the world
is full of people in need.
（カリナ）
世界中に困っている人がいるのは
分かっています
But I want to help my neighbors first.
（カリナ）
でも私は まず隣人を助けたい
Those I can reach out and touch.
手を伸ばして届く誰かを
That's the kind of government
I want to create.
そういう政治を
やっていきたいんです
This speech is a live broadcast, isn't it?
（雛河(ひなかわ)）この演説ライブ
生出演… ですよね？　これ
Yeah, it's live.
（如月(きさらぎ)）生よ
Direct appeals are more effective,
since they influence the citizens' Hues.
こういうのは
直接 訴えたほうが―
都民の色相にも影響を与えて
効果的なのよ
The Neighbor Policy was formulated by the
Affirmation Party, which endorsed Komiya.
隣人政策は
小宮を推薦した肯定党(こうていとう)の方針だ
They actually just want to regulate
immigrants and protect their interests.
入国者を規制して
自分たちの利益を―
守りたいってのが本音だ
You're sure politically minded, Irie.
入江さん こういうの詳しいですね
（観客たちの歓声）
Inspector!
（雛河）監視官！
What happened?
（雛河）どうしたんですか？
（如月）何？　何かの病気？
What is it? Is he sick?
Hello?
Doctor.
（志恩(しおん)）はあい？
先生 慎導(しんどう)監視官がおかしくなった
Something's up with Inspector Shindo.
Side effects of a Mental Trace.
（炯）メンタルトレースの副作用だ
This is a serious case.
これはひどいな
Should we administer an anxiolytic?
（志恩）抗不安薬を投与する？
No, he'll be fine.
（炯）いや 大丈夫だ
Hey, what are you doing?
（志恩）ちょっと 何する気？
Calling him back.
呼び戻してくる
But I want to help my neighbors first.
（カリナ）
私は まず隣人を助けたい
Those I can reach out and touch.
手を伸ばして届く誰かを
Arata.
（炯）灼
Arata!
灼！
Arata.
灼
（灼）ん…
Kei...
炯…
So, you're back, you idiot.
戻ったか バカ野郎
You're quick to call me an idiot.
すぐバカって言う
You've been diving too much.
（炯）最近 潜りすぎだ
You're under too much strain.
負荷が積み重なっている
ハァ…
Never mind me. Look into Karina Komiya.
それより 小宮カリナ
She's hiding something.
彼女には何かある
I got unofficial complaints from
two gubernatorial candidates today alone.
（霜月）今日だけで―
２人の都知事候補から
非公式の抗議が来たわ
They were unofficial?
（灼）非公式ですか
That's a relief.
それなら安心ですね
Internal Affairs sent us a warning
to stop interfering in the election.
（霜月）総務省からは―
選挙妨害をやめろと
厳重注意されたわ
So, what did you find?
で どうなの？
Any criminal activity?
事件性はあるの？
As of now, the death seems accidental.
今のところ ただの事故死です
What do you think you're doing?
うう… 何なの？　あなたたち
Playing a game of "how close can we get
to getting Chief Shimotsuki fired"?
２人で“霜月課長のクビを飛ばそう
危機一髪ゲーム”でもしてるの？
I wouldn't play that. It sounds boring.
そんな つまんなさそうなゲーム
しませんよ
（霜月）んっ！
But say there's a risk of terrorism.
（灼）それよりテロの危険が
That's a possibility?
え… そんな可能性があるの？
Yes, ma'am. I believe a precautionary
investigation is permitted in that case.
はい
であれば 予防的な捜査が
許されると思うのですが
"We're not interfering in the election.
Just the opposite, in fact..."
選挙妨害など めっそうもない
むしろ その逆だ… と
That was a surprise. Was Dr. Tsuchiya's
research really that dangerous?
（炯）驚いたな
土谷博士の研究
そんなにやばいのか？
Well, I'm not sure.
いや よく分からない
That's underhanded...
って お前な
Chief Shimotsuki realizes that.
霜月課長も そこは分かってるよ
Making it a precautionary anti-terror
investigation helps us deflect complaints.
テロの予防
選挙前の消毒ってことなら―
抗議を突っぱねられるし
Is Karina Komiya hiding
something that critical?
（炯）それだけの何かが
小宮カリナにあるのか？
I've never seen a mind like hers.
（灼）あんな心 初めて見た
It's thinking at frightening speeds,
but it's empty.
恐ろしい速さで思考してるのに
空っぽだ
Empty? She seems ambitious to me.
空っぽ？　野心的な人物なのに？
A mind like that could force someone
to weigh their Hue against their life
そういう人間が 誰かの色相と命を
てんびんにかけて―
and make them choose death.
死を選ばせるのかもしれない
Like the transport drone crash?
輸送機事故のようにか
Or like our case.
あるいは 俺たちの事件のように
ん…
If that's true...
もし そうなら…
Then she's connected
to the truth we're seeking.
彼女は 俺たちが求める真実に
つながってる
（志恩）ふう…
I cross-referenced
the hotel's security data.
ホテルの防犯データに
クロス検索をかけたわ
Now, pop quiz: What did I find?
（志恩）ここでクイズです
一体 何が出てきたでしょうか？
Pop quiz?
クイズって…
That's too simple to be
a quiz question.
簡単すぎて
クイズにならないですよ
ん…
Are you guys yanking my chain?
あの… みんな
俺をからかってます？
Just spit it out, Arata.
灼 さっさと言え
Fine. A Yakushiji staffer was staying
at the hotel where Dr. Tsuchiya died.
えー 薬師寺陣営のスタッフが―
土谷博士が死んだホテルに
泊まってた
Correct.
正解
Kosuke Yakushiji's first secretary
Lee Aki was staying at the hotel.
ホテルに泊まってたのは―
薬師寺康介(こうすけ)の第一秘書 リー･アキ
It's too much to be a coincidence.
（如月）偶然にしては
できすぎてるけど…
I guess this is the only lead we have.
突破口は これしかないですね
Delivery complete.
（運搬業者）配達終了でーす
（ドアの閉まる音）
I was not aware
of Dr. Tsuchiya's presence.
土谷博士がいたとは知らなかった
It was a coincidence.
I have nothing to hide.
偶然だし
後ろめたいことは何もない
（天馬）フン
I can check that with a Dominator
if you like.
ドミネーターで
確かめてもいいんだぜ
Do as you wish. It won't help you.
（リー）勝手にしろ 無駄なことだ
Mr. Lee, you tried to make contact
with Dr. Tsuchiya.
リーさん あなたは
土谷博士と接触しようとした
But you couldn't, because the bodyguards
from the Komiya campaign stopped you.
でも小宮側がつけた
ボディーガードが邪魔で―
それができなかった
You wanted inside info
on an opposing candidate.
あなたは対立候補の
内部情報を手に入れ―
You probably thought that Dr. Tsuchiya
was Karina Komiya's Achilles' heel.
土谷博士こそ―
小宮カリナのアキレス腱(けん)に
違いないと思ったんでしょう
Nonsense.
くだらない
Please don't make me
draw my Dominator.
本当にドミネーターを
抜かせないでください
I don't want to inconvenience the hotel.
ホテルにも迷惑がかかりますので
I told you to point it at me if you like.
したいなら向けろと言っている
I won't.
やめておきましょう
Instead, let me ask this.
Does Mr. Yakushiji know
代わりに質問ですが―
あなたと土谷博士が
同じホテルにいたことを―
that you were in Dr. Tsuchiya's hotel?
薬師寺さんは ご存じなのですか？
Mr. Yakushiji doesn't bother
to check my every movement.
先生が私ごときの居場所を
いちいち確認することはしない
I'll ask him, then.
じゃあ 本人に尋ねてきます
Please wait here.
ここで待っていてください
You have two minutes.
（リー）ハァ… ２分だ
I'll make it quick.
大急ぎで確認しますね
You seem awfully devoted
to Candidate Yakushiji.
薬師寺候補に
心酔しているようですね
Countless athletes have suffered setbacks,
despite having Sibyl suitability.
シビュラ適正が
あるにもかかわらず―
挫折したアスリートは
数えきれない
Mr. Yakushiji is the only person
who genuinely supports people like them.
だが そうした人々を
本気で支援してくださるのは―
先生だけだ
I see. And he save you, too?
（入江）ふーん
おたくも それで救われたと
Yes, he did. No one is more qualified
to be Tokyo's leader.
そうだ
あの方こそ
東京のリーダーにふさわしい
He's a hero born to be on top.
トップに立つために生まれた英雄だ
Area Stress Alert.
Perform psychological care immediately.
あっ
（コミッサ）エリアストレス警報
至急 メンタルケアを
行ってください
（炯）うっ
（入江）うおっ
（炯）ぐは！　うっ…
（入江）ふっ！　ああ…
ぐわ！　ううっ
Health check.
Your head has sustained a severe impact.
ヘルスチェック
頭部に危険な衝撃を受けています
There is a high probability
you are under assault.
あなたは暴行を受けている可能性が
極めて高いです
You don't say!
そうだよ
Evasive action recommended.
（コミッサ）
すぐに回避してください
I would if I could, moron!
できるか ボケ！　うっ
な…
（男）ぐお！
（炯）んっ！
（男）うっ
ぐっ…
Who are you people?
うう… お… お前ら
何なんだ… ああっ
はっ！
Crime Coefficient is 305.
（ドミネーター）犯罪係数 305
Lethal Eliminator.
Target for enforcement action.
リーサル エリミネーター
執行対象です
You gotta be kidding me!
（入江）うわっ クソ マジか！
What now?
（天馬）何だ！
（灼）逮捕しましょう
Arrest them.
Are you stupid?
Don't give me naïve crap.
バカか 甘ったれたこと
言ってんじゃねえよ！
（炯）ぐっ！
Temma, take the right.
（灼）天馬さんは右へ！
（天馬）うっ
Where'd he learn that?
何だ？　ありゃ
（炯）ぐっ ううっ
（男）うっ… んっ！
（男）うわっ
（炯）ぐっ！
（炯）んっ！
You're under arrest.
逮捕する
（荒い息）
You let him get away? Come on.
逃がしたのかよ ったく
Why did you stop me?
The Dominator said to enforce them.
さっきは 何で止めた？
ドミネーターは
執行しろって言ってたろうが
We need to exercise human judgment.
それを決めるのは
人間であるべきです
ん…
That's why the Dominator has a trigger.
そのためにドミネーターには
引き金がついてるんですから
I repeat: We have breaking news.
（キャスター）
緊急速報を繰り返します
Gubernatorial candidate Kosuke Yakushiji's
first secretary,
東京都知事に立候補した
薬師寺康介氏の第一秘書―
Mr. Lee Aki was assaulted and
brutally murdered.
リー･アキさんが―
暴行を受け
殺害されました
The killers announced the crime online
犯人は ネット上で
犯行声明を出し―
and allegedly committed hate speech
against Mr. Lee Aki's ethnicity.
リー･アキさんの人種に関わる
ヘイトスピーチを主張しています
That's filthy! Azusawa, you scumbag!
ぶっ！
（小畑(おばた)）汚(きたね)えぞ クソ梓澤！
うっ
Huh? What was that for?
え… 何で？　どゆこと？
I wonder whose down card
attacked the Yakushiji campaign.
（裁園寺）誰の伏せ札が
薬師寺陣営を襲撃したのかしら？
Even if one of us stepped forward
and claimed responsibility,
（代銀）仮にだ どちらかが
“私のです”と宣言しても―
would you believe us?
君は信用しないだろう
Invest in public-opinion-control AI bots.
（代銀）世論誘導用のＡＩボットに
インベスト
Dealing with the Relation Block can wait.
リレーションブロックの処理は
後回しだ
I also bet on public opinion control.
（裁園寺）こちらも同じく
世論誘導にベット
I propose resetting the priority
of Public Safety Bureau
私は 公安局刑事課一係の―
Criminal Investigation Department
Unit One.
プライオリティー再設定を
提案します
I object. The risk is too great.
（裁園寺）反対よ
リスクが高すぎる
It could easily alert Sibyl
to our existence again.
再び私たちの存在を―
シビュラに知らせる結果に
なりかねないわ
I concur.
（代銀）同意見だね
In that case,
I will dispose of the assets.
（静火）では
自分がアセットを処理します
Oh, my. It must be tough being the dealer.
（裁園寺）あらあら 親は大変ね
If you fail to dispose of them, Roundrobin
will take enforcement action against you,
処理に失敗すれば―
ラウンドロビンに執行されるのは
君だぞ 静火君
Understood, Shizuka?
If Kosuke Yakushiji
becomes governor of Tokyo,
（加工音声）
薬師寺康介が都知事になれば―
我々は外国人に
職も権利も奪われる
foreigners will take our jobs
and our rights.
We must not allow
the pro-immigrant faction to destroy
移民肯定派に この平和な社会を
破壊させては―
our peaceful society.
絶対にならない
As I thought, online opinion
（雛河）ネット上では やはり
小宮カリナ支持者の仕業―
is pretty unanimous that Karina Komiya
supporters are behind it.
という見方が強いです
Both Yakushiji
and the Eugenics Party that endorsed him
薬師寺も
やつを推薦した優生党(ゆうせいとう)も―
welcome anti-isolation policies,
after all.
入国政策を歓迎してるからな
To a thoroughbred like him,
野郎みてえな
サラブレッドにとっちゃ―
race doesn't matter
as long as they have good genes.
遺伝子さえ優秀なら
人種は関係ねえんだろうよ
And the corporate alliance behind them
しかも後ろについてる
企業連合は―
only care about hiring hordes
of immigrants as cheap labor.
入国者を大量雇用し 安く
働かせることしか考えてねえ―
They're all pieces of crap.
クソみてえな団体だしな
What's the actual likelihood
that the Komiya campaign is behind it?
実際のとこ 背後に
小宮陣営がいる可能性は？
（灼）うーん でも―
Well, Komiya's campaign manager
was an immigrant.
小宮候補のマネージャー
入国者でしたよ
She's been with Ms. Komiya
since she went independent.
（雛河）小宮候補が独立した時から
付き人だったようです
She might be breaking the party line.
党の方針に逆らってるのかも
That's probably just a front.
（炯）本音と建て前ってやつだろう
The Affirmation Party tacitly accepts
low-wage laborers too.
肯定党も
低賃金労働者の存在は黙認してる
Either way, the polls have flipped.
Yakushiji is the frontrunner.
何であれ支持率は逆転
薬師寺リード
Komiya is at a disadvantage.
小宮陣営が不利です
In the end, Inspector Shindo's prediction
was right on the money.
（霜月）結果的に大正解だったわ
慎導監視官の読みは
What prediction?
（灼）俺の読み？
About possible terrorism.
テロの可能性ってやつ さすがね
Good work.
I can't be happy about it.
喜べませんよ
People dying like that, whether
perpetrators or victims, is a tragedy.
加害者も被害者も
どんな理由であれ―
Whatever the reason may be.
ああいうふうに人が死ぬのは
悲しいことです
As for the man we arrested,
his background's a total blank.
逮捕した男は 背景を何も知らず
All assailants were from abandoned zones
and excluded from the census.
襲撃犯は全員 戸籍停止中で
廃棄区画の住人
Even if they moved through blind spots
in the street scanners,
街灯スキャナーの死角を縫って
移動するにしてもだ
could latent criminals really operate
openly over such a wide area?
こんな広範囲を―
潜在犯が堂々と動き回るなんて
できんのかよ？
And breaking into a hotel?
That should be impossible.
まして ホテルに侵入するなんて
普通 無理です
But not only did they get in,
one of them got away.
だが入ってきただけでなく
１人は逃げおおせた
It's clearly suspicious.
明らかに おかしい
（入江）ハァ…
Yakushiji has three campaign offices.
薬師寺陣営の選挙事務所は３か所
One in Ikebukuro, one in Suidobashi,
and one inside the Diet.
池袋(いけぶくろ) 水道橋(すいどうばし) そして国会内
Even if they could dodge street scanners,
they wouldn't have risked discovery.
連中に街灯スキャナーを
かわす手があったとしても―
見つかるリスクは避けたいはずだ
If I were them, I'd build a base
as close as possible and form a plan.
俺が犯人なら―
できるだけ近い位置に
拠点を築いて計画を立てます
You can get easy access to two of those...
（灼）その２つに
アクセスしやすいのは―
Myogadani
From Myogadani.
茗荷谷(みょうがだに)
Hey, wasn't the abandoned zone there
your old stomping grounds?
あそこの廃棄区画―
確か お前が昔
縄張りにしてたとこだな
（入江）ん…
The assailants must have come from here.
（入江）襲撃したのは
ここらの連中でしょう
They clearly practiced martial arts.
明らかに格闘技をやってた
Yes, they were versed
in hand-to-hand combat.
（炯）確かに
対人格闘に慣れていた
That's unusual under the Sibyl System.
シビュラシステムの下では
普通じゃない
There's a place where it is usual.
それが普通の場所があるんですよ
Signal lost.
（コミッサ）通信障害
Relays are required for Dominator usage.
Proceed with caution.
ドミネーターの使用に
中継機が必要です
ご注意ください
Shut up. I know that.
うるせえな 分かってるよ
Hey. Long time no see.
（入江）よう 久しぶり
Irie.
（用心棒）入江…
（観客たちの歓声）
A human-on-human combat arena.
人間同士の格闘場…
If Yakushiji is the public champion,
that's the underground champion.
薬師寺が
表のチャンピオンなら―
あれが裏社会のチャンピオンだ
Broker of the abandoned zone,
Haruki Enomiya.
廃棄区画のブローカー 榎宮(えのみや)春木(はるき)
Ex-pro athlete, and an ex-woman.
元プロアスリート 元女性
Retired in disgrace after overuse
of male hormones and body modifications.
男性ホルモンの過剰注射と
肉体改造の果てに無念の引退
So, would they know Yakushiji?
（炯）じゃあ
薬師寺と面識があっても…
I wouldn't be surprised.
（入江）不思議じゃない
Enomiya's Hue deteriorated
due to body changes and a poor record.
榎宮は肉体の変化と
成績不振で色相が悪化
And when they left center stage,
they built themselves a castle here.
そして表舞台から姿を消すと
ここに やつは城を建てた
Sounds like our culprit.
犯人ぽーい
That's why I brought you here.
そう思ったから
連れてきてやったの
Thank you. I'm counting on you.
感謝してます 頼りにしてますよ
Hey.
ああ… ん…
（ゴング）
（観客たちの歓声）
Enomiya gets athletes
with clouded Hues to fight here,
（入江）榎宮は 色相が濁った
アスリートをここで戦わせ―
taking bets on their matches
while raising strong soldiers.
ギャンブルの対象にしながら
強い兵隊を育ててる
We've got a suspect.
（灼）容疑者 発見
Now we just need a way to move fighters
without triggering street scanners.
あとは街灯スキャナーに
引っかからず―
格闘家を運ぶ方法だけ
Then let's haul Enomiya in
for questioning.
では早速 榎宮を連行しよう
Whoa there, are you stupid?
おいおい バカか？
Just look around.
見りゃ分かんだろ
They're the head of a huge organization.
What if they make a fuss?
こんだけ でかい組織のトップだぜ
騒ぎになったらどうする？
We didn't come here to start a war.
別に戦争をしに来たわけじゃない
Yes, just to ask questions.
そう 聞くだけ
Very funny.
面白(おもしれ)え
All right, Inspector,
I'll work something out.
じゃあ 監視官 俺が話つけますよ
It's been a long time, Mr. Irie.
（大石(おおいし)）お久しぶりです 入江さん
Looks like you're doing well, Oishi.
大石 元気でやってるみてえだな
This is a one-time deal.
こういうのは一度きりですよ
I know. Thanks.
分かってる ありがとな
I see you haven't changed.
あなたは
昔と何も変わってませんね
（入江）ん？
Right this way.
どうぞ 中へ
Voluntary questioning?
（榎宮）任意同行だと？
Yes.
（灼）はい
Interesting.
面白い
You've got promise.
君たち いけるね
Are you unawhere of where you are,
or are you just that confident?
ここがどんな場所か
分かってないのか―
異常な自信家なのか
Either way, you've got nerve.
どっちにしても いい度胸だ
We're not idiots or overconfident.
バカでも自信家でもない
Questioning suspicious people
is a detective's job.
怪しいやつには話を聞く
それが刑事だ
Osamu, sit.
（榎宮）オサム 座れ
Let me ask you a question, then.
（灼）じゃあ 質問しますね
Do you recognize this face?
この顔に見覚えは？
As you can see, this place is free,
unlike the world outside.
見てのとおり
ここは外の世界とは違い 自由だ
You can't expect me
to remember every face.
いちいち記憶には残らない
I hear you raise fighters here.
（炯）格闘家を
ここで育てているらしいな
As merchandise.
But none of them can leave here.
商品として
だが 皆 ここから出られない
Just like ferocious animals in a zoo.
動物園の猛獣と同じだ
But ferocious animals in zoos
are properly trained.
（灼）動物園の猛獣は
ちゃんと調教されてます
Oishi.
（榎宮）大石
Yes, Boss.
はい
Open your mouth.
口を開けろ
Yes, Boss.
はい
うっ！
Eat it.
食え
Yes, Boss.
はい
（大石のせき込み）
They're trained, just like circus animals.
サーカスの猛獣と同じで
調教済みだ
That's enough. Leave us.
もういい 下がれ
A circus, huh?
サーカスね
I'm disappointed in you, Kazumichi Irie.
入江一途(かずみち) お前も残念だ
You used to be the sharpest man we had.
最高にとがった男だったのに
And yet you ended up a Public Safety dog.
I didn't even have to break you.
私が調教してやるまでもなく
公安局の犬に成り果てるとはな
Don't talk like you know me.
知った口 利いてんじゃねえよ
What lout have you
been wagging your tail for?
てめえこそ どんなクソったれに
尻尾振ってんだ？
Don't get the wrong idea.
勘違いすんじゃねえぞ
フッ
I'm still as sharp as I ever was.
俺は 今も最高にとがってる
（水音）
（入江）う… いいい…
Ouch, that hurts!
痛(いて)え～ ふう…
What did you get all worked up for?
（天馬）お前が熱くなって
どうすんだよ？
Sorry.
（入江）すまん
Enomiya's a likely suspect, but why
would they attack the Yakushiji campaign?
容疑者としては濃厚だが―
榎宮が薬師寺陣営を攻撃する
動機が分からんな
Wouldn't it be for money?
金じゃねえのか？
I doubt anyone could pay Enomiya
and keep their Hue clear.
榎宮に金 渡した時点で―
そいつの色相も
無事じゃ済まないだろうな
If the Sibyl System got serious, it could
stamp out the abandoned zones easily.
シビュラシステムが本気になれば
廃棄区画を潰すのは簡単です
What would they stand to gain
that'd be worth that risk?
その危険を冒してまで
手を貸すメリットはあるのかな？
Weren't these zones abandoned
because they'd be too hard to rebuild?
（天馬）廃棄区画ってのは
復興が難しいから放置されたんだろ
They were left deliberately.
（炯）あえて そうしてるんだ
To cut costs nation-wide and give people
outside them mental breathing room.
国全体のコストカットと―
ここ以外で暮らす人々の
心の余裕のために
A spontaneously-occurring safety net.
（灼）自発的に生じた
セーフティーネット
Packaging complex systems of unforeseeable
crimes in isolated areas as slums
予測できない犯罪の複雑系を―
スラム型の隔離地域に
パッケージングして―
made them easier to monitor.
監視しやすくしたんですよ
The abandoned zones themselves are
a part of psychological care, so to speak.
（炯）言うなれば
この廃棄区画そのものが―
メンタルケアの一環ってわけだ
This place isn't a garbage dump.
ここはゴミ捨て場じゃねえよ
（灼）あ～ もやし うまかった～
Those bean sprouts were great.
What was your impression, Arata?
Of Enomiya, I mean.
灼の印象はどうだった？
榎宮について
（ゲップ）
（灼）うう… 犯人
A criminal. Not the mastermind,
so probably an accomplice.
黒幕は別にいるから共犯かな
What's your basis for saying that?
そう言い切れる根拠は何だよ？
If someone asked you to come in
for questioning, you'd want to know why.
任意同行なんて言われたら
その理由が気になりますよね
But Enomiya
asked almost no questions.
でも榎宮さんからの質問は
ほとんどなかった
No "Why me?" or
"What am I suspected of?"
“なぜ俺を？”とか
“何の容疑だ？”とか そういうの
Well, now that you mention it...
（天馬）ああ そういや そうだな
There are three questions left.
分からないことは３つ
One, how did they send attackers into
an urban area and avoid street scanners?
１つ 街灯スキャナーを避けて
襲撃犯を市街地に送り込んだ方法
Two, what was in it for Enomiya?
２つ 榎宮のメリット
And the third?
３つ目は？
How was the ramen so delicious?
I still can't believe it.
（灼）何でラーメンって
あんなにうまいんです？
（灼）信じらんな～い
（天馬）くっ…
Don't ask me!
（灼）ハハッ ハハハ…
（天馬）知るか！
Long time no see, Second Inspector.
（梓澤）久しぶり
セカンド･インスペクター
What's this about? You must be busy.
（榎宮）どうしたんです？
忙しいでしょうに
（梓澤）ハハッ
またまた とぼけちゃって
Oh, don't play innocent.
What was that attack?
何だい？　あの襲撃
Part of the Relation.
リレーションの一環ですよ
A congressman included me in their plans.
コングレスマンの誰かが
この私をプランに入れた
I know that.
そんなことは分かってる
I'm asking about your sloppy execution.
俺が気になったのは
ずさんすぎる手口だ
I just imitated the First's methods.
ファーストのやり方を
まねただけです
That was nothing like mine.
全然 違う
I always ensure my target
finish themselves.
俺は必ず
相手に自分自身を始末させる
What I do is art.
What you do is a half-baked copy.
俺のは芸術で
君のは中途半端な模倣だ
Are you getting anxious?
もしかして焦ってるの？
Worried that I'll steal the rank of First
you worked so hard for?
せっかく手に入れた
ファーストの地位を奪われそうで
Hardly. I would never...
フン まさか 俺はそんな…
Wait, that means...
てことは…
I see. That's what this is about.
そっか そういうことか
Hey, Azusawa.
おい 梓澤
I've heard enough.
もういい
I know how this incident will end.
今回のインシデント
結末が分かった
I'll start the clean-up. Bye.
後始末に入る それじゃ
It seems you're advancing successfully.
（却一郎）順調に
勝ち進んでいるようだな
Yes, Father.
（静火）はい お父さん
As you should. I raised you to win.
（却一郎）当然だ
勝つために お前を育てた
Discard any emotion that gets in your way.
邪魔な感情は すべて捨てろ
Win at any cost.
どんな犠牲を払ってでも勝て
If it helps you win,
使えるなら自分の命も使え
you should even use your own life.
Yes, Father.
はい お父さん
（ホテルマン）ん？
Sir.
お客様
Excuse me.
（ホテルマン）失礼します
This area is for the owner's personal use.
ここから先はオーナー専用の
エリアとなっております
I am the owner.
（静火）ここのオーナーです
No, I believe it's someone else...
（ホテルマン）
いや 確か別の方で…
As of today, I'm the owner.
I invite you to confirm it.
今日から私がオーナーです 確認を
I will survive.
必ず俺が生き残ってみせる
Mrs. Maiko Maya Stronskaya,
please come in.
（看護師）舞子(まいこ)･マイヤ･
ストロンスカヤさん どうぞ
An ordinary ocular prosthesis won't allow
your wife to regain her eyesight.
（医師）奥様の目は通常の義眼では
視力を取り戻すことはできません
With the latest surgical techniques,
however, success is highly likely.
ですが 最新の手術ならば―
成功する見込みは極めて高いです
Thank you very much.
ありがとうございます
We'll provide our best staff for the wife
of a Public Safety Bureau inspector.
（医師）公安局監視官の奥様には
最高のスタッフを用意しますよ
Sorry. I know you have work.
（舞子）出勤前にごめんなさい
Don't worry. I let Arata know.
大丈夫だ 灼には伝えてる
How long do I have to wait?
（男性）いつまで待たせるんだ！
Please, sir, wait your turn.
（看護師）ですから
順番に従ってください
（男性）あっ
Why did an immigrant get seen before me?!
入国者が
何で先に診察を受けてる！
Not so loud. This is a hospital.
静かに ここは病院ですよ
Get out, foreigner!
出ていけ 外国人！
Public Safety Bureau.
I don't want to make matters worse.
公安局勤務だ 事を荒だてたくない
You work for the Public Safety Bureau?
お前が公安局員？
What's this country coming to?
この国は どうしちまったんだ
I won't accept it!
わしは認めんぞ！
I won't let you have this country!
貴様らなんぞに
この国は渡さんぞ！
Sorry, I ran late.
（炯）悪い 遅くなった
It's fine.
The briefing's just about to start.
（灼）大丈夫
ちょうど今からブリーフィング
So, if we start by saying that Enomiya
is going rogue,
で 榎宮が
暴走してるって切り口なら―
we should get
the abandoned zone's cooperation.
廃棄区画の連中も協力するはずだ
It's best if we reached
an amicable resolution.
（灼）何事も
穏便に済むのが一番ですよ
OK, Inspector. I'll get to gathering intel
around the abandoned zone.
（入江）オーケー 監視官
廃棄区画中心に
早速 情報を集めるよ
I'll go with him.
（灼）俺が同行します
I knew you'd say that.
（入江）そう来ると思ったぜ
（灼）ぐわ～
In that case, Todoroki and I
will investigate the victims.
灼が襲撃したほうを
調べるなら―
俺と廿六木は
襲撃されたほうを調べよう
You don't mean...
なっ… まさか
Yakushiji's election office and committee.
薬師寺の選挙事務所と後援会だ
No thanks. You know my reasons.
嫌だね 理由は分かってんだろ
There are things only family would notice.
家族だからこそ
気づくこともあるだろ
That's why I can't understand them.
家族だから理解できねえんだよ
Obey your superior's orders!
監視官の命令に従え！
Understood.
分かったよ
You should come at night next time.
We'll take care of that little boy, too.
（女性）次は夜に来なよ
そっちの坊やも
かわいがってあげるから
（女性）ウフフッ
（灼）ハハ…
Everyone trusts you, huh, Irie?
みんな 入江さんを
信用してるんですね
Well, I like the people here.
まあ 俺は
ここの連中が好きですから
A lot of them are hopeless,
but they're all full of life.
どうしようもねえやつも多いが
みんな生き生きしてる
I think so, too.
（灼）俺も そう思います
あ…
You became an enforcer
to protect this place, didn't you?
（灼）だから ここを守るために
執行官になったんですよね
I never said...
（入江）俺は別にそんな…
You're a weird inspector.
フッ お前 変な監視官だな
Give it a rest!
（春馬）おい 貴様ら！
いいかげんにしたまえ！
（薬師寺の泣き声）
Who let them in here?
誰がここに通したんだ！　クソ！
（薬師寺の泣き声）
Lee... I...
私は…
We will arrest the...
（炯）我々は犯人を逮捕しよう…
（一童）黙れ！
Silence!
How insensitive must you be
to interview a man in his condition?
こんな状態で事情聴取なんて
無神経にも程がある！
Mr. Yakushiji is a victim!
先生は被害者なんだぞ！
（薬師寺の泣き声）
Let me be blunt, Temma.
（春馬）天馬 はっきり言ってやる
This is no place
for a latent criminal like you.
ここは お前みたいな潜在犯が
来るところではない
We live in different worlds.
住む世界が違うんだ
How far must you drag
our family name through the mud?
（一童）貴様 一族の名を
どこまで辱める気だ？
You must know all the slander
Father suffered because of you.
父上がお前のことで
どれだけ誹謗(ひぼう)中傷を受けたか―
知らんわけでもないだろう
You're just like my pathetic stepmother.
（一童）惨めな義母そっくりだ
（天馬）くっ…
Since you inherited inferior genes,
I don't consider you my brother.
劣等遺伝子を受け継いだお前は
兄でも何でもない
Just a latent criminal.
ただの潜在犯だ
Just disappear like she...
あの女のように早く消え…
（殴る音）
（倒れる音）
ハァ ハァ…
（一童）こ… 公安局の横暴だ
This is abuse of authority!
I'll have you fired!
お前をクビにしてやる！
You're suspended until the bureau chief
orders otherwise.
（霜月）
局長から指示が出るまで職務停止
Your Crime Coefficient and
inspector suitability will be reassessed.
犯罪係数と監視官適正の
即時再診断
The final decision
will be made after that.
この他は再診断後に決定します
Any questions?
質問は？
None, ma'am.
ありません
Say, Inspector.
（天馬）なあ 監視官
What is it?
Don't give me that.
What were you thinking?
（炯）どうした？
“どうした”じゃねえよ
何やってんだ！
No causal link has been proven between
Crime Coefficient and blood relation.
（炯）犯罪係数と血縁関係における
因果関係は立証されていない
His remarks were not
in accordance with Sibyl.
彼の発言は
シビュラ的ではなかった
（天馬）ハァ…
（炯）だが…
That said,
I acted out of order.
（炯）余計なことをした
I'm sorry.
すまない
I guess that wasn't very inspector-like.
まあ
監視官のやるこっちゃねえわな
What? Suspended from duty?
はあ？　停職処分？
That airhead kid is going to investigate
the assault case alone?
襲撃事件―
あの電波お坊ちゃんだけで
捜査するの？
You must be joking.
冗談でしょ
Those two are certainly good
at making messes bigger.
騒ぎを大きくするのが得意だよな
あの２人
If they're that concerned with accidents,
they might look into past inspectors'.
あれほど事故にこだわるなら―
前任監視官の事故の件も
ちゃんと調べてくれるかも
Don't bring that up out of the blue.
（如月）いきなり
変なこと言わないでよ
The chief already closed the case, right?
もう課長が
調査を打ち切ったでしょ
If they investigate, we latent criminals
will just get roped in.
調べたところで また―
潜在犯の私たちが
巻き込まれるだけよ
More importantly, nerdy kid,
それより なあ オタク小僧
aren't you done checking on them yet?
まだ２人の調べは終わんねえのか？
Huh? I found the inspectors'
career data ages ago.
えっ 監視官のキャリアデータ
とっくに見つけましたよ
Tell us that sooner, man.
早く言えよ 先輩
Let's see what we got.
どれどれ
Arata Shindo, age 24.
（如月）慎導 灼 24歳
Special-A-class profiler
with high empathic abilities.
高度な共感能力を持つ
特Ａ級プロファイラー
Recommended for assignment by...
Akane Tsunemori?
配属時の推薦者は…
あの常守(つねもり) 朱(あかね)？
You mean the killer ex-inspector?
人殺しの元監視官じゃねえか
Inspector Tsunemori is a great person.
常守監視官は立派な人です
I heard she was a top-notch
inspector who lost her mind.
超優秀だったけど
頭おかしくなっちゃったんだろ
His mother chose euthanasia due to illness
when he was young.
（如月）幼いころに
母親は重病で安楽死を選択
His father killed himself.
父親は自殺
His father, Atsushi Shindo, was a former
top Ministry of Welfare official.
父親の慎導篤志(あつし)
元厚生省官僚のトップの１人
Talk about a spoiled rich boy!
（天馬）マジ ボンボンじゃねえか
Information on the suicide is restricted.
（如月）自殺については閲覧不可
It's level three classified.
I can't retrieve it.
（雛河）機密レベル３(スリー)です
さすがに読み出せません
Anyway, after euthanasia and a suicide,
I'm amazed his Hue didn't cloud.
何があったにしても
安楽死に自殺なんて―
よく色相が曇らないわね
Anything on Inspector Ignatov?
イグナトフ監視官のほうは
何かねえか？
24-year-old Russian
naturalized Japanese.
（如月）
24歳のロシア系帰化 準日本人
Military training from his home country.
Excels in shooting, combat, and analysis.
母国で軍事訓練を受け
射撃 格闘 解析に優れた元兵士
Recommended by Chief Shimotsuki.
推薦者は霜月課長
Wow. I didn't know
Inspector Ignatov was married.
へえ イグナトフ監視官 既婚者か
His wife is Maiko Maya Stronskaya, 24.
（雛河）妻は
舞子･マイヤ･ストロンスカヤ 24歳
She's visually impaired
and undergoing treatment.
（如月）視覚障害者で現在 治療中
So he lives together with his blind wife?
目が見えない奥さんと
２人暮らし…
His brother, Akira Vasily Ignatov, was
also naturalized, but died two years ago.
兄の輝(あきら)･ワシリー･イグナトフも
帰化日本人だが―
２年前に死亡
Was he murdered?!
殺された？
The suspect in Akira Vasily Ignatov's
murder was... Atsushi Shindo?
（如月）
輝･イグナトフ殺害の容疑者は―
慎導篤志？
So, Inspector Shindo's father killed
Inspector Ignatov's brother, then himself?
つまり 慎導監視官の父親は―
イグナトフ監視官の兄を殺して
自殺した？
What kinda relationship is this?
何なんだ？　この関係は
The surviving family of a killer
and his victim became a buddy team?
被害者と加害者の遺族同士が
バディーを組んでるってわけかよ
It's definitely pretty out there.
（入江）だいぶクレージーなのは
間違いないな
There's a reason they stick together.
離れられない訳がある
The bond between them must be that strong.
それほど強い絆があるってことか
Having both lost family, they may have
had no choice but to trust each other.
家族を失った者同士―
むしろ お互いを
信じ合うしかなかったのかも
That's our Mao, always a romantic.
さすが真緒(まお)ちゃん ロマンチック
Who said you could call me that?
なれなれしい呼び方しないで！
（入江）うっ！　あ痛っ
You're such a pig...
（如月）ったく もう あんたは
（入江）あ… あ痛…
Temma should have been born
with a genetically perfect Psycho-Pass.
（春馬）天馬は―
遺伝的に完璧なサイコパスを持って
生まれたはずだぞ
Are you saying it's my fault?
（天馬の母）
私のせいだって言いたいの？
Your deteriorating Hue proves it.
（春馬）お前の色相の悪化が証拠だ
Tokorozawa Correction Center
Amazing how much difference
a mother makes.
（一童）母親の違いで
こんなに差が出るとはね
Great Sibyl assessments and gene editing,
but mother and son both latent criminals.
シビュラ判定も
遺伝子編集も最高なのに―
母子そろって潜在犯落ち
Shut up.
（天馬）黙れ
I'll cut to the chase.
（一童）本題に入ろう
（天馬）ん…
You see, Temma,
兄さん 実はね…
your mother died last week.
あなたの母親が先週 死んだ
え…
She took her own life.
（一童）施設で自殺したそうだ
That saved me the trouble
of disposing of her.
処分してもらう手間が
これで省けたね
ハァ…
Gimme a break!
ふざけんじゃねえ
What? You didn't tell Mai?
（灼）え？
舞(まい)ちゃんに言ってなかったの？
That's awful.
引くなあ
I planned to tell her later.
（炯）あとで
言うつもりだったんだよ
What on Earth were you thinking?
ホント 何を考えてるの？
Striking a civilian? I can't believe it!
民間人に手を上げるだなんて
信じられない
He flew off the handle
when someone insulted his colleague.
（灼）仲間の悪口を言われて
怒ったんだって
Kei's so kind.
炯は優しい
You always lose your cool
too quickly, dear.
あなたは昔から
すぐ頭に血が上るんだから
Think about what you did.
ちゃんと反省して
I will.
はい
Wouldn't a food printer
be easier on you, Mai?
フードプリンターのほうが
舞ちゃん 楽じゃない？
What? After she cooked for you?
（炯）作ってもらって
何言ってるんだ
The printer can't make
the food from my motherland.
プリンターじゃ故郷の味が出ない
I don't want to forget the dishes
my mom taught me.
母から教わった料理を
忘れたくないじゃない
That's true.
（炯）そうだな
Besides,
isn't it better than synthetic food?
何より 合成料理より
おいしいでしょ
Yeah.
うん
Sorry for holding you back.
足を引っ張って すまない
Don't worry about it.
（灼）気にしてないよ
Your Crime Coefficient and inspector-
suitability reevaluation were both clear.
犯罪係数も監視官適正の再診断も
クリアだったんだから
That means the Sibyl System understands.
シビュラシステムは
分かってくれてるってことでしょ
I hope so.
だといいがな
ハァ…
Is the case going well?
調査は順調か？
I'm missing a key piece of the puzzle.
肝心なパズルのピースが
見つからない
I'm pretty sure
Candidate Komiya is hiding it.
たぶん 小宮候補が
隠してると思うんだけど
Final Public Debate: Karina Komiya
vs. Kosuke "Heracles" Yakushiji
What about security for the debate?
公開討論会の警備は？
Unit Two is handling it.
（灼）二係が担当
（炯）そうか
I see.
（あくび）
Getting enough sleep?
（炯）最近は眠れてるのか？
ん～ どうかな…
Not sure.
Your skill puts strain
on both your brain and mind.
（炯）お前のスキルは
脳にも心にも負担をかける
You shouldn't use it so frequently.
そう頻繁に行っていいものじゃない
If the investigation requires it,
I'll have to.
捜査に必要なら
無理してでもやらなきゃ
Part of my job is not letting you.
（炯）そうさせないのも
俺の仕事だ
Aren't you suspended?
停職中のくせに？
I suppose I am.
（炯）それは… そうだが…
I'll do anything
if it means reaching the truth.
俺は真実に手が届くなら
何でもするよ
You're not the only one.
（炯）お前だけが
そう思ってるわけじゃない
Just don't do it
when I can't hold your rope.
俺がロープを
握れない時にはやるな
I'm sorry about the other day.
（灼）こないだのは反省してるよ
I can't see what you can.
お前に見えているものが
俺には見えない
So at least let me back you up.
なら せめて
バックアップは任せろ
Aren't you suspended?
停職中のくせに？
Drop it.
しつこいぞ
I'll get reinstated soon.
すぐに復帰してみせる
Why did Mai, you, and I
all have to lose family?
（灼）舞ちゃんも炯も俺も―
何で みんなが家族を
失わなきゃならなかったのか―
We'll find out together.
俺たち２人で見つけるんだ
うん
♪～
Stupid perfection in your own castle
How smart. You cause me to yawn
Look,
The key to the door is in your hand
Don't you let anyone take control
What do you want?
Go get it. Play by your own rule
The winner always controls the game
You stand in your belief
There's no promising future
Always helpless
Crying for the moon
Finger trembles in fear
With the weight of the trigger
There's a way for us
Show them how we fight
Pull the trigger
～♪
To fill the gap left by Inspector Ignatov,
（霜月）イグナトフ監視官の
穴を埋めるため―
I've asked an investigation consultant
contracted with the bureau to join us.
公安局と捜査コンサルタント契約を
結んでいる方に来ていただきました
Let me introduce her.
紹介します
Former Unit One enforcer
and current freelance journalist,
元一係 執行官で
現在 フリージャーナリストの―
Yayoi Kunizuka.
六合塚(くにづか)弥生(やよい)さんよ
"Psycho-Pass" refers to the measurement
of a person's mind and personality.
This is a work of fiction. Any resemblance
to real persons or groups is coincidental.